Kevin Maguire

Full-Stack Developer

CONTACT INFO

Address: 356 Hatfield St. Apt C Northampton, MA 01060





TECHNOLOGY



Tools:

* * * Django



Version Control:



About:

As a student at Code Platoon, I'm learning to be a full-stack developer and plan to bring my acquired skills to my new career in tech: my military experience emphasized teamwork, communication and perseverance; and working fulltime as a 911 EMT increased my problem solving, emotional intelligence and resilience. I'm new to the tech industry and ready to go all-in.

Experience:

Code PlatoonFull-Stack Web Developer Bootcamp

Jan 2020 – Apr. 2020 Chicago, IL (Remote)

Education:

University of New Hampshire Bachelor of Science: Biomedical Science Fall 2016 Durham, NH

Interests:

- Jamming with Friends (guitar or drums)
- Finding a New Brewery (can't give Treehouse all my money)
- Trying New Hot Sauces (Pepper Palace is my church)
- Reading Books (especially self-development, philosophy and ideologies)
- Attempting the Art of Baking (starting with bread)

Employment:

Charter Communication

Field Technician

Feb. 2019 – Jan. 2020 *Worcester, MA*

- Excelled in customer service and maintains a 5/5 customer satisfaction rating for several months
- Repaired and troubleshooted telecommunication systems and company two for least repeats calls for two months straight
- Consistently rated within the top 40% of employees on all metrics
- Performed residential installations of telecommunication networks

American Ambulance Services

Emergency Medical Technician

Oct. 2014 – Nov. 2018 Somersworth, NH

- · Obtained primary 911 EMT after eight months of employment
- · Assessed nature and extent of illness or injury to establish and prioritize medical procedures
- Observed, recorded, and reported patient condition or injury, treatment provided, and reactions to drugs and
 - treatment to hospital staff and documented in post-run patient care report
- · Administered first-aid treatment and life-support care to sick or injured persons in prehospital setting

United States Army and NH National Guard

Officer Candidate & Signal Support Systems Specialist

Nov. 2011 – Present Concord, NH

- Responsible for all encryption and communication security.
- Training manager for communication and IT systems
- Supervisor for junior enlisted teams from 5 to 20
- Responsible for equipment in excess of \$400,000